<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Python on Justin Pearson</title><link>https://justinkennethpearson.github.io/tags/python/</link><description>Recent content in Python on Justin Pearson</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-uk</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://justinkennethpearson.github.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setting up Python notebooks locally for Machine Learning</title><link>https://justinkennethpearson.github.io/post/2022/01/28/setting-up-python-notebooks-locally-for-machine-learning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://justinkennethpearson.github.io/post/2022/01/28/setting-up-python-notebooks-locally-for-machine-learning/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is mainly for students on my machine learning course. I use a lot
of Python notebooks either for examples from lectures or for
assignments. While there are many options for hosting python notebooks
for free remotely, but I prefer to do things locally. If you wish to do
the same then please read on. Note that I did home some problems
installing &lt;code&gt;skikit-image&lt;/code&gt; on a new Apple with M1 silicon, but after
upgrading the latest version of the operating system and doing and
updating my &lt;code&gt;homebrew&lt;/code&gt; setup everything works. Note that these
instructions are for using &lt;code&gt;pip&lt;/code&gt;. If you are using an alternative
package manager such as &lt;code&gt;Anaconda&lt;/code&gt; then you are on your own. I know
nothing about setting up Python on a windows machine.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Creating and using Python Virtual Environments</title><link>https://justinkennethpearson.github.io/post/2020/12/10/creating-and-using-python-virtual-environments/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 13:51:33 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://justinkennethpearson.github.io/post/2020/12/10/creating-and-using-python-virtual-environments/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;In a lot of my courses I encourage students to use python virtual
environments. Virtual environments are a great way of making sure
that you have the correct version of packages installed.
This is very short cheat sheet on how to set them up. I
will assume that we are using Python 3. Luckily Python 3 has virtual
environments set up. It is all in the
&lt;a href="https://docs.python.org/3/library/venv.html"&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;, but then
sometimes people are too lazy to google, or do not know what to google
for. Of course this assumes that you are a command line person. If you
are using some IDE, then you are on your own.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>